
var quiz = {
"JS": [
{
"id": 1,
"question": "New Spider-Man Miles Morales was introduced in which Marvel comic series?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Ultimate Superheros",
"b": "Ultimate Spiderman",
"c": "Ultimate Comics: fallout",
"d": "Ultimate Spider-verse"
}
],
"answer": "Ultimate Comics: fallout;",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 2,
"question": "What's the name of Miles Morales' parents?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Rio Morales ans Jefferson Davis",
"b": "pinto Ramirez and Michigan Fortune",
"c": "Miranda Cortez and Hunderbart Underling"
}
],
"answer": "Rio Morales ans Jefferson Davis",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 3,
"question": "What is Miles doing when he is bitten by a spider?",
"options": [
{
"a": "graffiti",
"b": "Skating",
"c": "Homework"
}
],
"answer": "Graffiti",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 4,
"question": "What's the name of Kingpin's chief scientist?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Olivia Octavius",
"b": "Noctune",
"c": "Charlotte Witer",
"d": "Anna Kravinoff"
}
],
"answer": "Olivia Octavius",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 5,
"question": "Who does Miles NOT face in the final fight?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Octavius",
"b": "Scorpion",
"c": "Tombstone",
"d": "Scorcher"
}
],
"answer": "Scorpion",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 6,
"question": "What is Miles doing when he is bitten by a spider?",
"options": [
{
"a": "graffiti",
"b": "Skating",
"c": "Homework"
}
],
"answer": "Graffiti",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 7,
"question": "How do you call a function named &quot;myFunction&quot;?",
"options": [
{
"a": "call function myFunction()",
"b": "call myFunction()",
"c": "myFunction()",
}
],
"answer": "myFunction()",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 8,
"question": "What is strange about the spider that bites Miles?",
"options": [
{
"a": "its a robot",
"b": "it can talk",
"c": "it is radioactive",
"d": "it is large",
}
],
"answer": "it is radioactive",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 9,
"question": "What new power does Miles have?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Teleportation",
"b": "Invisibility",
"c": "Superspeed",
"d": "Telepathy"
}
],
"answer": "Superspeed",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 10,
"question": "What is strange about the spider that bites Miles?",
"options": [
{
"a": "its a robot",
"b": "it can talk",
"c": "it is radioactive",
"d": "it is large",
}
],
"answer": "it is radioactive",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 11,
"question": "What relation is Prowler to Miles Morales?",
"options": [
{
"a": "friend",
"b": "cousin",
"c": "uncle"
}
],
"answer": "uncle",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 12,
"question": "Whose particle accelerator opens the Spiderverse?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Venom",
"b": "Prowler",
"c": "Kingpin",
"d": "Lizard"
}
],
"answer": "Kingpin",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 13,
"question": "What colour is Spider-Man Noir?",
"options": [
{
"a": "black",
"b": "blue",
"c": "grey"
}
],
"answer": "black",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 14,
"question": "Who tries to teach Miles to use his powers?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Peter A Parker",
"b": "Peter B Parker",
"c": "Peter C Parker"
}
],
"answer": "Peter B Parker",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 15,
"question": "What new power does Miles have?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Teleportation",
"b": "Invisibility",
"c": "Superspeed",
"d": "Telepathy"
}
],
"answer": "Superspeed",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 16,
"question": "Which of the following Spider-People ISN'T real?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Spider-man",
"b": "Spider-gwen",
"c": "Spider-ham",
"d": "Spider-Nam"
}
],
"answer": "Spider-ham",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 17,
"question": "What is the name of Peter Parker's aunt?",
"options": [
{
"a": "april",
"b": "may",
"c": "june",
"d": "july"
}
],
"answer": "may",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 18,
"question": "What's the name of Kingpin's chief scientist?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Olivia Octavius",
"b": "Noctune",
"c": "Charlotte Witer",
"d": "Anna Kravinoff"
}
],
"answer": "Olivia Octavius",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 19,
"question": "What does Miles use to design his new costume?",
"options": [
{
"a": "glue and glitter",
"b": "spray-paint"
}
],
"answer": "spray-paint",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 20,
"question": "How does Miles overcome Kingpin?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Heat ray",
"b": "Web sling",
"c": "Venom blast"
}
],
"answer": "Venom blast",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 21,
"question": "Who does Miles NOT face in the final fight?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Octavius",
"b": "Scorpion",
"c": "Tombstone",
"d": "Scorcher"
}
],
"answer": "Scorpion",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 22,
"question": "What does Peter Parker give Miles after his fight with Green Goblin?",
"options": [
{
"a": "a key",
"b": "Usb drive",
"c": "a microchip"
}
],
"answer": "Usb drive",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 23,
"question": "How does the Spider-Verse get opened?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Some leaves a door unlocked",
"b": "Someone makes a particle acclerator",
"c": "Someone creates a spider laser",
"d": "someone creates a multiplier"
}
],
"answer": "Someone makes a particle acclerator",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 24,
"question": "New Spider-Man Miles Morales was introduced in which Marvel comic series?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Ultimate Superheros",
"b": "Ultimate Spiderman",
"c": "Ultimate Comics: fallout",
"d": "Ultimate Spider-verse"
}
],
"answer": "Ultimate Comics: fallout;",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
},
{
"id": 25,
"question": "What is Miles doing when he is bitten by a spider?",
"options": [
{
"a": "Graffitti",
"b": "homework",
"c": "skating"
}
],
"answer": "Graffitti",
"score": 0,
"status": ""
}
]
}
var quizApp = function () {
this.score = 0;
this.qno = 1;
this.currentque = 0;
var totalque = quiz.JS.length;
this.displayQuiz = function (cque) {
this.currentque = cque;
if (this.currentque < totalque) {
$("#tque").html(totalque);
$("#previous").attr("disabled", false);
$("#next").attr("disabled", false);
$("#qid").html(quiz.JS[this.currentque].id + '.');
$("#question").html(quiz.JS[this.currentque].question);
$("#question-options").html("");
for (var key in quiz.JS[this.currentque].options[0]) {
if (quiz.JS[this.currentque].options[0].hasOwnProperty(key)) {
$("#question-options").append(
"<div class='form-check option-block'>" +
"<label class='form-check-label'>" +
"<input type='radio' class='form-check-input' name='option' id='q" + key + "' value='" + quiz.JS[this.currentque].options[0][key] + "'><span id='optionval'>" +
quiz.JS[this.currentque].options[0][key] +
"</span></label>"
);
}
}
}
if (this.currentque <= 0) {
$("#previous").attr("disabled", true);
}
if (this.currentque >= totalque) {
$('#next').attr('disabled', true);
for (var i = 0; i < totalque; i++) {
this.score = this.score + quiz.JS[i].score;
}
return this.showResult(this.score);
}
}
this.showResult = function (scr) {
$("#result").addClass('result');
$("#result").html("<h1 class='res-header'>Total Score: &nbsp;" + scr + '/' + totalque + "</h1>");
for (var j = 0; j < totalque; j++) {
var res;
if (quiz.JS[j].score == 0) {
res = '<span class="wrong">' + quiz.JS[j].score + '</span><i class="fa fa-remove c-wrong"></i>';
} else {
res = '<span class="correct">' + quiz.JS[j].score + '</span><i class="fa fa-check c-correct"></i>';
}
$("#result").append(
'<div class="result-question"><span>Q ' + quiz.JS[j].id + '</span> &nbsp;' + quiz.JS[j].question + '</div>' +
'<div><b>Correct answer:</b> &nbsp;' + quiz.JS[j].answer + '</div>' +
'<div class="last-row"><b>Score:</b> &nbsp;' + res +
'</div>'
);
}
}
this.checkAnswer = function (option) {
var answer = quiz.JS[this.currentque].answer;
option = option.replace(/</g, "&lt;") //for <
option = option.replace(/>/g, "&gt;") //for >
option = option.replace(/"/g, "&quot;")
if (option == quiz.JS[this.currentque].answer) {
if (quiz.JS[this.currentque].score == "") {
quiz.JS[this.currentque].score = 1;
quiz.JS[this.currentque].status = "correct";
}
} else {
quiz.JS[this.currentque].status = "wrong";
}
}
this.changeQuestion = function (cque) {
this.currentque = this.currentque + cque;
this.displayQuiz(this.currentque);
}
}
var jsq = new quizApp();
var selectedopt;
$(document).ready(function () {
jsq.displayQuiz(0);
$('#question-options').on('change', 'input[type=radio][name=option]', function (e) {
//var radio = $(this).find('input:radio');
$(this).prop("checked", true);
selectedopt = $(this).val();
});
});
$('#next').click(function (e) {
e.preventDefault();
if (selectedopt) {
jsq.checkAnswer(selectedopt);
}
jsq.changeQuestion(1);
});
$('#previous').click(function (e) {
e.preventDefault();
if (selectedopt) {
jsq.checkAnswer(selectedopt);
}
jsq.changeQuestion(-1);
});